<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Something We Ate</title>
    <link>http://somethingweate.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Something We Ate</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 08:30:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://somethingweate.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>about</title>
      <link>http://somethingweate.com/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 08:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://somethingweate.com/pages/about/</guid>
      <description>Hey there! How are you?
Oh, you want to know about me? Since you ask, I&amp;rsquo;m going to take second to tell you a bit about me. By day I&amp;rsquo;m a developer. This should be obvious from the &amp;ldquo;social&amp;rdquo; link for Github. That&amp;rsquo;s where I keep all the code I write. Around the time my boys turned three years old, I got the itch to make. It&amp;rsquo;s not uncommon for developers (and everyone else) to want to take a step back and do something menial, monotonous, and engaging to our core motor skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taco Seasoning</title>
      <link>http://somethingweate.com/posts/taco-seasoning/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 07:48:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://somethingweate.com/posts/taco-seasoning/</guid>
      <description>So one of my white whales (I have many) is taco seasoning. Growing up in northern MN, &amp;ldquo;tacos&amp;rdquo; always meant ground beef + packet of taco seasoning. Sure you can mix in veggies, hard/soft shells, lettuce for taco salad, blah blah blah. That&amp;rsquo;s what tacos always were to me. Then I found Nacho&amp;rsquo;s.
Before I go any further, let me say that their logo does not represent the food, atmosphere, or people at Nacho&amp;rsquo;s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peach Jam</title>
      <link>http://somethingweate.com/posts/peach-jam/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 07:58:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://somethingweate.com/posts/peach-jam/</guid>
      <description>So I&amp;rsquo;ve had a lot of fun discovering Jam (and by extension, preserving). It was largely inspired by a video series on tastemade. Kevin West taught the class on jam based entirely on his book Saving The Season. It&amp;rsquo;s a fantastic video series and the book is great. It&amp;rsquo;s particularly nice that he goes into explaining jam. I like to understand what I&amp;rsquo;m doing and really hate recipe books that just give you recipes without teaching you to understand what you&amp;rsquo;re doing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe Manager</title>
      <link>http://somethingweate.com/posts/recipe-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 13:40:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://somethingweate.com/posts/recipe-manager/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re going to organize your recipes any one way, I&amp;rsquo;d like to recommend onetsp. They are a very affordable, on-line recipe manager that hits all the geek buttons (markdown, web clipper, extra notes, export, et. al.).
I&amp;rsquo;ve been a happy customer for a few years and the only complaint I have is the inability to alter tags in bulk. You can share recipes via email. Overall, if you&amp;rsquo;re looking to digitize your recipes, this is the tool I&amp;rsquo;d recommend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books I&#39;ve Read</title>
      <link>http://somethingweate.com/posts/books-ive-read/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2017 12:00:00 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://somethingweate.com/posts/books-ive-read/</guid>
      <description>Every now and then, I see someone asking about good books. Further, I often can&amp;rsquo;t call to mind some of the better books I&amp;rsquo;ve read in the moment. To that end, I&amp;rsquo;m going to list out some of the better books I&amp;rsquo;ve read. Keep in mind, I mostly read non-fiction so the number of fiction books to call upon is pretty slim.
In no particular order, these are some books I would recommend.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>